https://www.iwheadlines.com/privacy-policy/

Home
History
You are here: Home / Information / Privacy PolicyUpdated July 4, 2014
Created November 12, 2009
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us.
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the IWHeadlines.com website.
On some pages, you may be solicited to join e-mail mailing lists and/or register to enter contests to receive awards.
The types of personal information that may be collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when entering a contest only until that contest is over.
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive.
Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our e-mail newsletter as well as updates on new additions, products, and services available on this website.
Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the e-mail newsletter registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to personally identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, our host has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important.
For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting info.request [@] iwheadlines [dot] com.
We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error along with the information that you would like to be updated.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Google Analytics Remarketing:
This website uses Google Analytics and their remarketing program.
Under this program, in addition to data collected through the standard implementation of Google Analytics, data is also collected about our traffic from Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers.
IWHeadlines.com will never facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google advertising product or feature unless we provide robust notice of, and the your prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger.
To opt-out of having your non-personally identifiable demographic information tracked, we encourage you to use this link provided directly by Google.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us by using our online form located here, sending mail to Usable Web Solutions, LLC at P.O. Box 119, Oakhurst, NJ
07755, or sending us an email at policy.question [@] iwheadlines [dot] com.
Latest News
» IMPACT Plus Celebrates Rich Swann
Posted on November 19, 2020» Final Impact Wrestling Bound for Glory Card (10/24)
Posted on October 24, 2020» Impact Wrestling 2020 TV Ratings
Posted on July 25, 2020» Current And Former Knockouts Defend Division Name
Posted on July 25, 2020» Michael Elgin Comments on Impact Wrestling Release
Posted on June 27, 2020» Tessa Blanchard Released, Stripped of Impact Title
Posted on June 26, 2020» AXS TV Expands Tuesday Nights With IMPACT in 60
Posted on June 1, 2020» Full Viewership Report for IMPACT Wrestling (7/15)
Posted on July 16, 2015» Full Viewership Report for IMPACT Wrestling (7/8)
Posted on July 9, 2015» Full Viewership Report for IMPACT Wrestling (7/1)
Posted on July 2, 2015
Multimedia
» Video: AEW Champion Kenny Omega Appears on IMPACT!
Posted on December 9, 2020» Video:
Kenny Omega Wins AEW Championship and Escapes with Impact Wrestling’s Don Callis
Posted on December 3, 2020» Video: The Rock Inducts Ken Shamrock into the Impact Wrestling Hall of Fame
Posted on October 25, 2020» Gallows & Anderson, “(Paul Heyman) Just 100% Full Of B.S.”
Posted on July 18, 2020» A Young Brian Cage Competing on TNA Gut Check
Posted on July 2, 2020» Video:
The Wolves Talk After Final Match with Dirty Heels
Posted on July 3, 2015» Video:
End of EC3 vs. Kurt Angle Championship Match
Posted on July 3, 2015» Video:
Jeff Jarrett Talks with Mike Tenay After Slammiversary
Posted on July 3, 2015» Video:
Robbie E. Talks After TNA Slammiversary
Posted on June 29, 2015» Video:
Bram Talks After Facing Matt Morgan at PPV
Posted on June 29, 2015
Results
» Impact Wrestling Slammiversary Results (7/18): New Champions, Returning Stars, & More!
Posted on July 19, 2020» IMPACT Wrestling Results (7/15):
Bully Ray Is Back
Posted on July 16, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (7/8):
EC3 Is In Charge!
Posted on July 9, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (7/1):
Bell to Bell ft. EC3
Posted on July 2, 2015» TNA Slammiversary Results (6/28):
New KOTM Champion!
Posted on June 29, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (6/24):
Live from Orlando!
Posted on June 25, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (6/17):
Lashley vs. EC3
Posted on June 18, 2015» TNA Destination X Results (6/10):
Spud vs. Angle
Posted on June 11, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (6/3):
Wednesday Night!
Posted on June 4, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (5/29):
May Mayhem!
Posted on May 30, 2015
Upcoming Events
» Impact Wrestling Slammiversary Results (7/18): New Champions, Returning Stars, & More!
Posted on July 19, 2020» IMPACT Wrestling Results (7/15):
Bully Ray Is Back
Posted on July 16, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (7/8):
EC3 Is In Charge!
Posted on July 9, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (7/1):
Bell to Bell ft. EC3
Posted on July 2, 2015» TNA Slammiversary Results (6/28):
New KOTM Champion!
Posted on June 29, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (6/24):
Live from Orlando!
Posted on June 25, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (6/17):
Lashley vs. EC3
Posted on June 18, 2015» TNA Destination X Results (6/10):
Spud vs. Angle
Posted on June 11, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (6/3):
Wednesday Night!
Posted on June 4, 2015» IMPACT Wrestling Results (5/29):
May Mayhem!
Posted on May 30, 2015
